Contact

9543260650 (Mobile) luisgornes@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/luisg-688356b5 (LinkedIn) luis33k.github.io/myPortfolio/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Full-Stack Development Incident Response Node.js

Certifications

CompTIA Cybersecurity Analyst+ (CySA+) (CS0-003) Cert Prep: 3 Incident Response and Management

Learning Relational Databases

Information Technology Support Specialist Technical Certificate

Project Management Foundations: Requirements

CompTIA Cybersecurity Analyst+ (CySA+) (CS0-003) Exam Tips

Luis Gornes

Full Stack Developer Computer Science & Information Technology Major (CS&IT) Tutor/Student Assistant @ Broward College

Fort Lauderdale, Florida, United States

Summary

Computer Science & Information Technology Major. Full Stack Web & Software Developer and Tutor/Student Assistant @ North Broward College for 4 years.

I tutor and assist students in C, C++, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Python, Batch, SQL, PHP

Information Technology: Web Development BAS Degree currently enrolled attending Broward College North campus, with 7 years of work experience.

Enrolled into my BAS program and working as Tutor on campus! Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of basic and advanced computer science skills to successfully fill the tutoring role in the computer lab at North Broward college. Frequently praised as helpful and knowledgeable by my peers, I can be relied on upon to help students understand, learn, and solve problems with my background in computer programming.

Experience

Broward College Student Assistant/Tutor January 2020 - Present (4 years 11 months) Broward County, Florida, United States

Computer Science & Information Technology Tutor at North Broward College.

I help tutor students in CS&IT programming.

Student Tutor (Computer Science Lab Tutor)

- Help any student who comes to me for help.
- · Monitor students activities online.
- Work on computer programming.
- · Make adjustments to time schedule.
- Fill out my hours for the week online

LightFire Distribution
Picker Packer Order shipper, Fulfillment specialist

Page 1 of 3

July 2021 - March 2022 (9 months)

Tamarac, Florida, United States

- Verifying picked orders
- · Picking orders around the warehouse
- Occasional warehouse maintenance/product origination

Dunkin'

Crew Member Barista

June 2019 - January 2020 (8 months)

Coral Springs, Florida, United States

- Taking customers' orders at a register.
- Preparing coffee orders, brewing coffee, mixing drinks.
- Preparing food orders, restocking, prepping food cleaning.
- Washing dishes, mopping, sweeping, throwing out trash including food, cleaning tables, whipping down stations restocking.
- Customer service, helping people fix issues they had with the order if any.

NETSER COMPUTER INTERNATIONAL, INC.

Robotics programmer

October 2018 - March 2019 (6 months)

Coral Springs, Florida, United States

- Creating designing Arduino based projects.
- Building actual working models/prototypes.
- Programming in C lang and Arduino language.
- Problem/error solving, team work, communicating.

ABB OPTICAL GROUP

Fulfillment Specialist

November 2017 - August 2018 (10 months)

Coral springs, FL

- Picking orders around the warehouse
- Verifying picked orders
- Occasional warehouse maintenance/product origination.

Education

Broward College

Associate's degree, Computer Science · (June 2017)

Cooper City High School · (2013 - 2017)